export const Questions = [
    {
        prompt: "What year did One Direction form?",
        optionA: "2010",
        optionB: "2012",
        optionC: "2008",
        optionD: "2011",
        answer: "A",
    },
    // {
    //     prompt: "What was One Direction's debut album?",
    //     optionA: "Midnight Memories",
    //     optionB: "Four",
    //     optionC: "Up All Night",
    //     optionD: "Take Me Home",
    //     answer: "C",
    // },
    {
        prompt: "Who was the oldest member of One Direction?",
        optionA: "Niall Horan",
        optionB: "Harry Styles",
        optionC: "Louis Tomlinson",
        optionD: "Liam Payne",
        answer: "C",
    },
    // {
    //     prompt: "Which album features 'Drag Me Down'?",
    //     optionA: "Up All Night",
    //     optionB: "Made in the A.M.",
    //     optionC: "Midnight Memories",
    //     optionD: "Four",
    //     answer: "B",
    // },
    {
        prompt: "Which member is Irish?",
        optionA: "Harry Styles",
        optionB: "Louis Tomlinson",
        optionC: "Liam Payne",
        optionD: "Niall Horan",
        answer: "D",
    },
    // {
    //     prompt: "What was One Direction's last album?",
    //     optionA: "Four",
    //     optionB: "Up All Night",
    //     optionC: "Made in the A.M.",
    //     optionD: "Take Me Home",
    //     answer: "C",
    // },
    {
        prompt: "What show formed One Direction?",
        optionA: "The Voice",
        optionB: "The X Factor",
        optionC: "American Idol",
        optionD: "Britain's Got Talent",
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which song starts with 'Written in these walls'?",
        optionA: "Perfect",
        optionB: "Story of My Life",
        optionC: "Night Changes",
        optionD: "Little Things",
        answer: "B",
    },
    // {
    //     prompt: "Which album features 'Little Things'?",
    //     optionA: "Up All Night",
    //     optionB: "Take Me Home",
    //     optionC: "Four",
    //     optionD: "Midnight Memories",
    //     answer: "B",
    // },
    {
        prompt: "Which song has the lyric 'Let's go crazy, crazy, crazy'? ",
        optionA: "Live While We're Young",
        optionB: "Kiss You",
        optionC: "No Control",
        optionD: "Best Song Ever",
        answer: "A",
    },
];
